surveypayoff.com 2018-10-02

# SurveySay: Get Paid To Take Surveys Online!

SurveySay ("we," "us," or "our") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of our online survey panels (the "Service") currently operated from SurveySay (the "Website"). We created this Privacy Policy to give you confidence and describe how we treat personal information as you visit and use our Service and Website. Click to Contact Us.

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the Site and the Service, as well as any other websites, applications, or services that link to this Policy. By providing information to us or by using our Website or Service, you explicitly agree to our collection and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. _If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website or Services._

Collection of Personal Information

We collect a variety of information from users, including email address, username, password, survey response information, log file information (such as IP address and browser data), and cookies.

Please note that in some cases, we need certain types of information so that we can provide you with the Service. If you do not provide us with such information, or ask us to delete it, you may not be able to obtain the Service.

 _Registration Information._ You need a username and password from us to access the protected areas of the Website. We require some limited personal information to create an account for you, including your user name, password, email address, mailing address and telephone number (optional). We also collect and maintain Social Security Numbers for any member whose points and rewards exceed $600 per year, only as required for tax reporting purposes.

 _Website Use._ When you use the protected areas of the Website, certain information about your use is automatically recorded and retained, such as account activity (e.g., number of log-ins), data displayed or clicked on (e.g., user interface elements, links), and other log information described below.

 _Survey responses and other submissions._ We may provide you opportunities to participate in surveys on our Website. If you participate, or apply to participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes background/demographic information, which might include, for example, as zip code, age, consumer habits or information about hobbies, interests, employment status and product ownership ("background/demographic information"). The requested information also includes members' survey responses to questions and issues of interest to us and our clients ("response information"). We also collect information volunteered by users of our Website, such as by completing and submitting our online forms, or emailing or mailing us.

 _Log file information._ When users visit our Website, our servers automatically collect certain information that the browser sends when visiting websites in general. This log file information may include the URLs you visited; your IP address; date, time, and time spent on pages visited; and information about your browser and platform.

 _Cookies._ From time to time, our Service and/or Website may use the "cookies" feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your use of the same. Cookies help us learn which portions of our Service and Website are useful and which need improvement, recognize your account when you visit our Website, and collect and analyze statistical information (e.g., date and time of visits to our Website), among other things. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your survey responses will not be tracked and you will not receive related points or rewards, and your experience with the Service otherwise may be significantly diminished. We may offer you the opportunity to participate in surveys for which a client requires additional cookies for those particular surveys. Those additional cookies would be used only with your approval.

 _Do Not Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms._ We do not respond to browser-initiated Do Not Track signals, as the Internet industry is currently still working on Do Not Track standards, implementations, and solutions.

 _Analytics._ We may use third-party Web analytics services in connection with the Website and Service, such as those of Google Analytics. These service providers use a variety of tracking technologies such as cookies to analyze how users use the Website and Service. The information collected (described above in “Cookies”) will be collected directly by these service providers to evaluate your use of the Website and Service. For more information on how Google Analytics uses data from our websites and how you can control the information sent to Google,[ click here.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please[ click here.](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) Because these opt outs are cookie-based, please note that if you get a new computer or device, install or start using a new browser, or erase or alter your browser’s cookie file, you may need to opt out again.

Use of Personal Information

 _Generally._ We use the personally identifiable information and aggregate/anonymous information we collect to:

  * maintain your account;
  * market and provide the Service and Website to you;
  * communicate with you, including emailing invitations or sending text/SMS alerts to you to participate in surveys;
  * determine your eligibility for and match you to particular surveys;
  * deliver points and rewards to you;
  * provide background/demographic information and response information to our clients in aggregate/anonymous form only;
  * secure and troubleshoot issues with the Site and Service;
  * improve our offerings;
  * create new offerings; and
  * protect the rights of SurveySay or others.

"Aggregate/anonymous" means to combine the member's information with the information of other members without identifying a specific member or to make data anonymous so that it describes the interest profile, demographics data and/or response of a particular member without specifically identifying the member.

In particular, we do not send "spam." The emails that we send after your registration will be to invite or alert you to participate in our surveys, to deliver points and rewards to you, or to send newsletters, updates, and other service or administrative notices. You may opt out at any time as described below under "Opting Out."

 _Registration Information._ We do not use your personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages to you (such as offers regarding the Service) without your consent or opt-in. We may send you certain service and administrative notices, which are not subject to opt out.

 _Background/demographic information and response information._ We always report background/demographic information, as well as response information, in aggregate/anonymous form to our clients. We also use this information to target our surveys and better interpret our survey findings.

 _Log file information and cookies._ We use cookies and log file information to remember your information so that you do not need to re-enter it when using the Service and Website, to provide personalized content, and to administer and monitor usage of the Service and Website.

 _Aggregate/Anonymous Information._ We use aggregate/anonymous data to analyze Website usage and customize the Website's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Website and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with an efficient and customized experience while using the Website. We also report background/demographic information and response information in aggregate/anonymous form to our clients.

Information Sharing

Generally, we share information, particularly background/demographic information and response information, only in aggregate/anonymous form with our clients, and only for their use for bona fide market research. In these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide the Website and Service:

  * We may share our information with our affiliates.
  * We may disclose your information if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with any law, regulation or order, such as subpoena, court order or search warrant;
  * We may share your information with our service providers, but only subject to a confidentiality agreement;
  * We may disclose your information to protect and defend our rights or property, including investigations and defense of third-party claims;
  * We may disclose your information to otherwise ensure compliance with our agreements, Terms of Use and policies; and/or
  * We may disclose your information to protect the rights, property and personal safety of our users, staff or the public.

We reserve the right, in the event all or any relevant portion of our stock, business or assets is transferred to, acquired by or merged with any third party, to transfer or assign as part of such transaction any or all of the information we have collected. We may also share your information during due diligence regarding such a transaction.

Account Corrections

You may access or change your account settings logging into your personal profile on the Service or contacting us using the information in the “Contacting Us” section below. Any changes you make to your account settings generally take immediate effect. However, we may retain any information to the extent required by law or otherwise in connection with the permitted information sharing described above.

Opting Out

You may terminate your membership by clicking the unsubscribe link at the footer of any page of our Website when you login or at the footer of emails that we send. Please allow forty-eight (48) hours for the unsubscribe to process. Parents or legal guardians of any member who is under the age of eighteen (18) similarly may discontinue their child's participation. We will retain all information collected prior to termination in our databases indefinitely.

Links

The Service and Website and content on them may contain links to other sites and resources controlled by third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites or resources, and you should consult the privacy statements of such other sites and resources.

Data Security

Our Service and Website have security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is absolutely secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We remind you to keep your username and password private. We do not request passwords in unsolicited emails or telephone calls. Also, we suggest you log out of your membership account with us and close your browser window after completing a survey or other activity from our Website. This will better protect your privacy if you are sharing a computer or accessing the web from a library or other public place.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy, including the use of your information for new, unanticipated purposes, at any time by posting a revised version on the Website, and/or sending information regarding the amendment to your email address of record with us. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Website to obtain timely notice of such amendments. You shall be deemed to have accepted such amendments by continuing to use the Service and/or Website after such amendments have been posted or information regarding such amendments has been sent to you. If you do not agree with any of such changes, you may immediately cease all access and use of the Service and Website. You agree that such termination will be your exclusive remedy in such event.

International Users

Our computer systems are currently based in the United States, so your personal data will be processed by us in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. By using the Website or Service, you agree to this Policy and you consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States, which may not offer a level of protection equivalent to that required in the European Union or certain other countries, and to the processing of that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Children’s Privacy

The Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information (as defined by the United States Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act) from children under the age of 13. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 13 who has provided her or his information to us, please contact us through the means listed below and we will seek to remove that information.

California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

SurveySay does not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their services to you unless you first agree to such disclosure. If you have any questions regarding this policy, you may contact us using the information in the “Contacting Us” section below.

Miscellaneous

To the extent there are conflicts between the English language version of this Privacy Policy and versions of this policy in other languages, the English language version of this Privacy Policy will control.

Contacting Us

If you have any questions, suggestions, or complaints, please contact us by clicking here: Contact Us.

 **Effective date of this version:** July 1, 2018
